原創翻譯  雙語字幕
最新連載海外影視劇下載
請登陸 www.YYeTs.com
僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
翻譯     一只蝦  Royaa
翻譯     小酸奶
校對     小酸奶
時間軸     房內注意安全羅大  腦子被漿糊住紙袋
后期     8T
總監     小酸奶
人人影視Pro
人人影視官方唯一APP
在線觀看，離線緩存，百度云
app.YYeTs.com
官方網站下載 : 人人影視Pro
最新海外影視劇下載
人人影視Pro
人人官方唯一APP
在線觀看，離線緩存
屏方APP
掃碼下載
介個APP成精了
能幫你扒同款☛
104號房間
第一季第十集
都是灰塵
It's dusty.
只有熱風
Just hot air.
什么
What?
你還好嗎
You okay?
還行  幾點了
Yeah. What time is it?
九點四十
Nine forty.
你渴嗎
Are you thirsty?
我們剛剛不應該休息的  都怪我  抱歉
We shouldn't have stopped. It's my fault. I'm sorry.
我經常想著  我有一天會去那里的
Like I said, I just always thought I'd go there someday,
所以就可能像...
so it seemed like maybe a...
沒關系
It's okay.
我們還有時間
We have time.
你電話設置好了嗎
You have the phone ready?
我小時候經常跟我爸去蘭堡球場看比賽
My dad and I used to go to games at Lambeau when I was little.
綠灣包裝工隊是橄欖球聯盟里
You know, the Packers are the only
唯一一支由公眾共同擁有的球隊
community-owned team in the NFL.
1984年的時候  教士隊的老板
Well, the owner of the Padres
也想要資助這球隊
tried to donate the team
去代表美國圣迭戈市
to the city of San Diego in 1984,
但法律不允許
but the league wouldn't allow it.
系統阻止了
The system prevented it.
電話設置好了沒
You have the phone ready?
搞定了  我預留了60秒
Yeah, I gave it 60 seconds before it goes,
在電話之后
you know, after the call arms it.
兄弟  介意我進去嗎
Hey, um, mind if I come in?
-進來  -嗯
- Come in? - Yeah.
別  我在忙呢
Yeah, no, I'm working.
或許你可以休息一下
Maybe take a break just for a minute.
我們可沒有時間休息
We don't have a minute.
你剛剛才說我們還有時間
You said we have time.
如果我們不休息的話
Not if we take a break.
-我要進來了  -不要啊
- I'm coming in. - No!
-我的天  你小心點  -進來能讓我安心點  好嗎
- Oh, Jesus, be careful! - Look, it'll relax me, okay?
只是
Just...
出去
Get out.
你知道這有多精細嗎
Do you know how delicate this is?
當然知道
Of course.
你想把我們倆都害死嗎
You wanna get us both killed?
我會很小心的
Look, I'll be careful.
這里面更熱了
It's even hotter in here.
抱歉我沒能修好那空調
Sorry I couldn't get the AC going.
所以我們要怎么處理這帳篷
So what do we do with the tent?
等我們完事之后
I mean, when we're done.
-燒了嗎  -為什么要燒掉
- Burn it? - Why would we burn it?
有我們的基因  證據
DNA. Evidence.
所以我們才在里面弄  不是嗎
That's why we're in here, right?
-可以洗啊  -對
- A tent can be washed. - Right.
可如果他們在我們到達目的地前
What if they check the bag, you know,
要檢查這包呢
before we get to the spot?
-堅持我們的說法  -好
- Stick to the story. - Right.
-簡單明了  -對
- Short and simple. - Right.
-就兩句話  還記得嗎  -記得
- Two sentences, remember? - Yes.
會沒事的
You'll be fine.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
抱歉
Sorry.
我只是
I just...
都這時候了  這也不重要了吧
I mean, at this point, what does it matter?
跟我說說那支隊伍
Tell me about the Packers.
你去看的第一場比賽
First game you went to.
你不用轉移我的注意力
Oh, you don't have to Jedi mind trick me.
我沒事
I'm fine.
那時我八歲
I was eight.
我本來都不知道  但歷史上
And I didn't realize it then, but historically,
那場確實是關鍵賽
it was a really significant game.
你聽說過蘭博之躍[一種慶祝方式]嗎
Have you ever heard of the Lambeau Leap?
瑞吉·懷特從對方獲得進攻者的漏球
R-Reggie White recovered a fumble from the Raiders
然后橫向傳給了勒魯瓦·巴特勒
and he lateraled it to LeRoy Butler
由他帶球跑到25碼觸地得分
who took it in 25 yards for the touchdown.
為了慶祝  他跳進了看臺的第一排
And to celebrate, he jumped into the first row of stands
一大群粉絲
and a bunch of the fans,
有老有少
I mean, old men, grown men,
他們跟他擁抱然后拍拍他的背
they just hugged him and patted him on the back.
蘭博之躍
The Lambeau Leap.
這大概是他們第一次
Probably the first time
與黑人接觸
any of them had ever touched a black man...
也包括我父親在內
my dad included.
如果他沒有贏呢
What if he doesn't win?
我要吐了
I'm gonna throw up.
喝點水吧
Drink some water.
我快弄完了
I'm almost done.
你還好嗎
You okay?
我可以把電視打開嗎
Mind if I turn on the TV?
你想看就打開吧
If it makes you feel better, go ahead.
...記者正在會議中心...
...our correspondent is live at the convention center...
真的嗎
Really?
來了很多人...
There's a big crowd...
不能換個臺嗎
You can't do better than this?
你換好衣服了嗎
You getting dressed?
你先洗個澡吧  一身臭汗
You might wanna shower first. It's like a swamp in here.
今晚史密斯成為代表
Gonna be a wild one
場面一定會非常壯觀
down there tonight as Smith works the delegates...
支持者認為今晚能有和他交流的機會
Supporters believe tonight is the chance to talk to his base,
實際上  今晚他將著力
but the truth is tonight should be all about
說服大家他能勝任總統這份職務
convincing people that he can do the job and be presidential.
人們能想象到他在白宮的場景嗎
Can people picture him in the White House?
這正是問題所在
That's the question.
他的話能引起拿不定主意的選民的共鳴嗎
Will his message resonate with undecided voters?
今晚聚光燈將給他大約一小時的時間
The spotlight will be on him tonight for about an hour
展現自己說服大家
to see if, you know, he can accomplish just that.
也有些好消息  邁克
There's some good points here, Michael.
絕對是這一周的壓軸好戲
Definitely a big finale to a long week.
我們有必要知道每一次大會都是
I think it's important to know that each convention
獨一無二的
has its own story to tell,
我做不到  對不起
從開幕敲槌到最后的掉球儀式
from the opening gavel to the final balloon drop.
-操  -他們想賦予大會
- Fuck! - They're trying to create the narrative
人的性格
of conventions as people.
而這里的選民
What's happening here is that
投票結果是無法預測的
people are proving to be unpredictable in the polling.
...他生命中最關鍵的一次演講
...is one of the most critical speeches of his life.
一名代表說大多數選民
One delegate told me a considerable portion of the electorate
并不看好他有當總統的能力
simply did not see him as presidential.
他得向眾人展示
His challenge is to reveal himself
他可以領導整個國家的氣魄
as someone who can lead a nation.
他沒法滿足所有人的要求
He cannot be all things to all people,
但他得說服這幾百萬選民
but his task will be to convince millions
他能勝任總統這份職務
that he's up for the job.
有人擔心會有人
There's been some concern that if someone
想要發言或采取行動
wanted to make a statement or do something,
今天正是行動的好時機
that today might be that day,
所以現場安排了很多警衛人員
so we are seeing a lot of police presence.
這絕對符合他的最大利益
It's definitely in his best interest to.
-同意  不過... -我靠
- I agree, but... - Holy shit!
天吶
Oh, my God.
-抱歉  -搞什么
- I'm so sorry. - What the hell?!
那個服務員讓我進來的
The maid let me in.
只有他能修好
He's the only one who can fix it.
我們敲了門
We knocked,
但電視太...
but this TV is so...
他有太多事情...
He's had a lot of things on his...
你可以一會再過來嗎
Could you just come back later?
我不是故意嚇你的
Um, I didn't mean to alarm you.
我一分鐘就能做好
I'll be done in a minute here.
最后一個了  弄好我就走了
It's my last one, and then I can get out of your hair.
直接回家
Go home.
抱歉沒有早點來  但今天人手不足
I'm sorry we couldn't come sooner, but we're a man short today.
其實我打算出門了
I'm actually on my way out.
你能給我十分鐘收拾行李嗎
Could you give me 10 minutes to pack up my stuff?
十分鐘嗎  我五分鐘就弄好了
Uh, 10 minutes? I'll be done in five.
-我趕時間  -好吧
- I'm running late. - Well,
我不影響你  你快收拾吧
don't let me stop you. Do what you gotta do.
現在做這個是不是有點晚了
Isn't it a little late for this?
有點  抱歉
Yeah, it is. Sorry about that.
今天真夠瘋狂的
It's been a crazy day.
因為這個會議市中心堵死了
Traffic in the city is a mess with this convention in town.
平時的路這會兒有三倍堵
I had to drive through the thick of it three times already.
因納貝特只剩一條小路可走
Innerbelt's down to one lane
希望路就更不用說了
and you can forget about Prospect.
我以為總算經過了堵的地段
I finally think I got a hold on all these road closures
結果到了這里又遇上了堵塞
and come out here and hit another massive jam.
一幫小孩們吵著抗議
Bunch of rowdy kids protesting,
把街上堵得水泄不通
getting into the street, messing up traffic.
老實跟你說
Look, if I'm being honest with you,
我馬上要結束今天十二個小時的工作了
I'm at the tail end of a 12-hour day,
我很想快點回家
I would just love to get home
陪我老婆看完演講
and see the rest of that speech with my wife.
請快點
Please hurry.
謝謝你
I do appreciate it.
不管怎么樣
Anyway,
真不知道你怎么能忍受這種溫度的
don't know how you could take this heat a minute longer.
你是進城來開會的嗎
You in town for the convention?
我看到你的東西了
I saw your, uh, thingy over there.
是的
Oh, uh, yeah.
我...我是進城來開會的
Yeah, I'm, uh, in town for the convention, yes.
看來你要遲到了
Well, I guess you are running late.
我保證我馬上就弄好
I'll have this done in a minute, I promise.
我有原則  不和房客討論政策
I kind of have a rule not to discuss politics with the customers,
但我想你在電視上應該都看到了
but I figured you got it on the TV, so.
是啊  顯而易見的事
Yeah, elephant in the room, so to speak.
是啊  的確很明顯
Yeah, he's some kind of elephant, that's for sure.
很難忽視
Tough to ignore.
你是這個意思嗎
Is that what you mean?
-是的  -是啊
- Yeah. - Yeah? Well...
他的人氣真的很高  對吧
He really gets the juices flowing, you know?
你不是代表吧
You're not a delegate, are you?
不然的話  你現在肯定在會場
I mean, if you were, you'd be in that arena right now, right?
我只是要去參加會后的酒會
I'm just going to the after party.
真不錯
Oh, very nice.
-是什么大人物嗎  -不
- Some kind of big shot? - No.
我明白
I hear ya.
朋友的朋友是個大人物  對吧
Friend of a friend of a big shot, am I right?
正如我所說
Yeah, like I said,
我一般不和房客討論政治
I usually don't talk politics with customers,
但這幾天城里的人嘴里說的都是這些
but it's all anybody wants to talk about in this town these days.
政治和體育
Politics and sports.
我們就不能直接投給勒布朗·詹姆斯嗎
I mean, can't we just vote for LeBron James?
我不是同性戀  但是
I'm not gay, but, boy,
要是勒布朗說要我嫁給他
I'd have to give it some serious consideration
我會考慮一下
if LeBron asked me to marry him.
我可能的好好考慮
I might have to rethink
我當初在同性戀婚姻提案中的立場了
my whole position on that gay marriage thing.
當然了  我只是在開玩笑的
I'm just kidding, of course.
挺好笑的
That's funny.
這里真是熱得像地獄一樣
Hot as the devil in here.
是啊
Yeah.
你的小家伙呢
Where's your little one?
小家伙
Little one?
我的孩子小時候
When my boys were young,
就喜歡在客廳搭堡壘
they used to build forts in the living room,
一般都用毯子和被子
usually with blankets and sheets.
不過好像沒用過真正的帳篷
Can't say they ever used an actual tent, though.
是啊  不  我們帶他去野營后
Yeah, no, um, ever since we took him camping,
他就喜歡上了
he's been obsessed with it.
客廳啊  后院啊  屋頂啊
You know, living room, backyard, roof.
我都習慣了  到處都是
I'm so accustomed to seeing it around,
我自己幾乎都沒注意
I barely even notice it anymore.
-他幾歲  -七歲
- How old is he? - Seven.
真的嗎
Really?
你看上去很年輕啊
You seem so young.
結婚早吧
Started early, I guess.
是啊  我的是18歲和22歲
Yeah, well, mine are 18 and 22.
瘋狂的小混蛋
Yeah, crazy, little bastards.
當然了  他們已經不小了
Of course, they're not so little anymore,
所以我想他們只是瘋狂的混蛋
so I guess they're just crazy bastards now.
柯蒂斯  我的長子  他上大學了
Curtis, my older one, he goes to college.
他讀的是個娘娘腔的專業  上帝啊
He's a women's studies major, God help us.
小兒子還在念高中
The younger one, he's still in high school.
他是州籃球隊隊員
He's a basketball player, all-state.
說實話  他們都是好孩子
Well, truth be told, they're both great kids.
總會讓你不禁想
You know, really gets you thinking
他們離開后會怎么樣
when they leave the house, I'll tell you that.
不知道他們會變成什么樣
Just don't know how they're gonna turn out.
只能盡力防守
Just do your best and let 'em go,
交叉手指
cross your fingers.
你說你的小孩在哪里來著
Where'd you say your boy was?
和我妻子一起在家里
At home with my wife.
對
Right, um,
我知道這看起來很奇怪
I know it looks weird,
但我喜歡出差的時候帶上
but I like to bring it with me when I travel.
能緩解對他的四年
It makes me miss him less.
那...那不錯
That's-- that's sweet.
-怎么樣了  -過幾分鐘...
- How's it going? - A few more minutes and...
就修好走人
I'll be out of your way.
好
Great.
你要來點嗎
You want some?
算了吧
I better not.
不過謝了
Thanks, though.
你覺得他能贏嗎
You think he can win?
他都走到了今天
He's made it this far.
是啊
Yeah.
不知道這個國家有沒有準備好接受如此真實的領導
I just wonder if this country's ready for someone so real.
但是到了十一月  我會給他投票
But come November, he's got my vote.
真不錯
Good to hear.
移民  北美自由貿易協定  中東的這些亂子
Immigration, NAFTA, the whole mess in the Middle East.
你們這些人講得都是有模有樣的
Oh, your guy really tells it like it is.
我們這些人
My guy?
不過我告訴你
I'll tell you what, though.
不管誰贏了  街上都會
Whoever wins, there's gonna be
有一大群氣壞了的家伙
an army of pissed off people roaming in the streets.
上帝啊
Fucking Christ!
你能小心點嘛
Careful, would ya?!
對不起
I'm sorry.
不
No, um,
我...我反應過度了
I just-- I overreacted.
對不起
I'm sorry.
沒事
Ah, it's-- it's okay.
我也有緊張的時候
I'd be on edge, too.
今晚對你來說很重要
It's a big night for you.
我修好后  馬上就走
I'll just finish up here and then I'll-- I'll be on my way.
還愿意給我酒嗎
That offer still stand?
我也不想那么說  但我有點潔癖
Ah, I hate to be that guy, but I'm kind of a germ freak.
能給我搞個杯子嗎
Think you could get me a cup?
好的
Sure.
給
Ah, here you go!
Here you go.
這一天真是漫長
It's been a long day.
真不錯
Oh, nice.
味道真不錯  謝謝
That is very nice. Thank you.
小波本威士忌
Small batch bourbon.
是我一個朋友在肯塔基制的
A friend of mine distills it in Kentucky
然后100一瓶賣給布魯克林的嬉皮士
and sells it to hipsters in Brooklyn for $100 a bottle.
一百
A hundred bucks?
看來各有所愛了
Wow, everybody's got an angle, I guess.
不是嗎
Don't they?
不好意思
Excuse me.
沒事吧
Everything okay in there?
沒事  馬上就好
Yeah, just, uh, give me a second.
-LG的一次性電話吧  -是的
- An LG burner, am I right? - Yep.
我干過幾年手機修理
Yeah, I spent a few years in phone repair.
要給我看看嗎
Want me to have a look?
不用
No.
你確定嗎
You sure?
好了
There you go.
一切都沒事吧
Everything okay?
如果你有一臺時光機
If you had a time machine...
你能回到過去
and you could go back in time
阻止希特勒變成希特勒...
and prevent Hitler from becoming Hitler...
你會去的  對嗎
you have to do it, right?
時光機
A time machine?
是啊  就像《回到未來》
Yeah, like "Back to the Future."
德洛雷安
A DeLorean.
每小時88.8英里  你就能回到過去
88.8 miles per hour, you can go back in time,
你能回到1930年的德國
specifically, you go back to Germany circa 1930,
你和希特勒在一個城市
you're in the same city as Hitler,
一個房間  你有一把槍
same room, you have a gun.
你會動手嗎
Do you do it?
會吧
Yeah.
-我想我會的  -你會嗎
- I guess I would. - You would?
是啊
Yeah.
我是說  謀殺的確是沒啥
I mean, murder is murder.
的確是一種罪
It'd still be a sin, I suppose,
但那好像是正義的
but that one would seem justifiable.
我想我會有那個勇氣
I'd like to think I'd have the guts to do it.
對
Right.
不過要是那個時光機壞了
Get pretty sticky, though,
那可就難辦了
if that time machine broke down.
我是說  你殺了希特勒后
I mean, after you killed Hitler.
肯定很難跟在場的那些人解釋
It'd be a tough one to explain to the folks in the moment.
"相信我  伙計們  他會做一些壞事"
"Believe me, people, he was gonna do some bad things."
我覺得值得做出犧牲
I think it'd be worth the sacrifice,
想到自己阻止了大屠殺
knowing you prevented the Holocaust.
晚上也能安心入睡
I could sleep at night.
但誰知道會不會有第二個希特勒呢
But who's to say another Hitler wouldn't be waiting in the wings?
另一場大逃殺
You know, a different Holocaust?
只靠一個人是無法殺死兩百萬猶太人
I mean, one person alone didn't kill two million Jews.
-六百萬  -那更加說明我的觀點了
- Six million. - Okay, more to my point.
我們算是幫助這個人
So we somehow associate this one man
造成這么多人死亡
with all these millions of deaths...
-是謀殺  -但不是他扣下的扳機
- Murders. - ...but he wasn't the one pulling the triggers.
對吧  不是他扔下的炸彈
Right? He wasn't the one dropping the bombs.
我不知道
Eh, I don't know.
我現在重新考慮  也許我不會動手
I'm rethinking this now. Maybe I wouldn't.
-你不會  -是的
- You wouldn't? - No.
你是說你選擇不干掉那個
So you're saying you wouldn't take out the person
策劃戰爭奪走
who devised and implemented the destruction
一千一百萬人生命的人
of 11 million human lives?
你剛剛說六百萬
You said six million.
六百萬猶太人  五百萬其他人
Six million Jews, five million others.
如果我知道那樣做能阻止這些屠殺
Well, if I knew that it would prevent those deaths,
那當然了  但我要說的是萬一不能呢
then, yeah, sure, but what I'm saying is what if it didn't?
但是  嘴上說
And anyway, it's easy to say,
"如果我見到希特勒  我會..."很簡單
"If I could've met Hitler, I would've..." Blah, blah, blah,
但沒人做到過
but nobody ever did.
所以說明很多人肯定同意他的做法
So that means a whole lot of people must've agreed with him.
你覺得是嗎
You think so?
也許他們也恨猶太人
Maybe they hated the Jews, too.
足夠殺死六百萬人嗎
Enough to kill six million of them?
足夠接受這件事
Enough to go along with it.
我不知道  他們在那個年代可能就會那樣
I don't know, could be they were living in hateful times.
對
Right.
我說了  回頭想想
Like I said, it's easy to look back
說自己會更好  是很簡單的事
and say you would've been better.
-我們會拒絕  -沒錯
- That we'd resist. - Yeah.
-我們會做些什么  -是的
- That we'd do something. - Sure.
問題是  我們沒有時光機  不是嗎
Thing is, we don't have a time machine, do we?
你沒看到我的德洛雷安停車在外面嗎
You didn't see my DeLorean parked out front?
不好意思
Sorry.
是我妻子  我得接一下
Uh, it's my wife. I have to take this.
我真的快修好了  我馬上回來
I really am almost done. I'll-- I'll be right back.
親愛的
Hey, honey.
會議入場證
金色權限
看上不真不錯
Whoa, looking sharp!
我該走了  你可以待在這里修好空調
I should really get going, but feel free to stay and finish up.
好吧
All right, well,
等你回來后  這房間會非常涼快清爽
room will be nice and cool for you when you get back.
謝謝
Thanks.
順便  你可能會見到我兒子
By the way, you might run into my son.
他參與的學校社團
He's part of a school group
這周都在參加會議
that's been at the convention all week,
我妻子剛告訴我
and my wife just told me
他們今晚也受邀參加派對
they got invited to that party tonight.
所以他特別激動
So he's pretty jazzed about it.
他叫杰瑞
His name's Gerry.
不是說你肯定會遇到他  但是誰知道呢
Not that you'll run into him, but who knows?
-杰瑞  -對  我叫史蒂夫
- Gerry. - Yeah. I'm Steve.
和你聊的很愉快
Nice chatting with you.
亞歷克斯
Alex.
很高興見到你  亞歷克斯
Good to meet you, Alex.
今晚玩得開心
Have fun tonight,
祝你11月好運
and good luck in November.
謝謝
Thank you.
我要再去一次廁所
I'm actually gonna hit the bathroom one more time.
媽媽
爸爸說你這周五不來了
下周末呢
我再聯系你
我愛你
都修好了
All done!
-太好了  -是啊
- Great. - Yeah.
你看看
Check it out.
不了  我該走了
Nah, I-- I should go now.
站在我站的位置  亞歷克斯
Stand where I'm standing, Alex.
感受一下
See how it feels.
我要遲到了
I'm late.
你在流汗
You're sweating.
來
Come on.
相信我  你等下會謝我的
Believe me, you'll thank me later.
-我真的應該...  -坐下
- I should really-- - Sit down.
還有那東西嗎
Still got that thing in there?
你的杯子
Oh, your cup.
小波本
Small batch, huh?